{"question": "How old is your wrapping paper?", "answer": "Oh my gosh! Years! I have some paper that my SIL bought me before she was married to my brother and they\u2019ve been married 21 years. It has Boyd Bears on it and I don\u2019t want to use it.\nI also found a bag last year that had a tag on it with my moms name and she\u2019s been gone since 2011.\nSome of my bags are way older than that though.\nFun question!"}
{"question": "If you are in a Christmas gift exchange and the rule is not to spend more than $150, what\u2019s the minimum you feel you have to spend?", "answer": "The spending limit means not above that, not it must be that. Any amount below is acceptable,"}
{"question": "If you won a billion and a half dollars, what would you do with the money?", "answer": "Some states allow you to collect the money in secret, but my state isn\u2019t one of those. And I figure someone would figure it out and announce it, so your idea of moving is probably for the best.\nAfter seeking professional advice on tax shelters etc., the sharing comes in.\n\nFamily would come first and foremost. Friends and coworkers. Then donations to the animal shelters, St. Jude\u2019s childrens hospital and homeless shelters and food banks in my state.\n\nI would set up a fund to pay all kids breakfast and lunches in my state for as long as the money held out. Even the families that could afford the lunches should get it. That way, the less fortunate wouldn\u2019t be as noticeable. My state is one of the poorest in the nation, so helping get kids food and clothes would take a large portion of my money.\nOf course I would move also, and travel."}
{"question": "Do you buy gifts for friends and family when you travel?", "answer": "I really haven\u2019t traveled too far from home. But whenever we go to a beach I love to collect seashells and pretty little stones I find and sometimes give them to family. So this may not qualify. I have never been to another country\u2026ooh that would be so cool!"}
{"question": "Do you have any interesting/sweet sympathy gift ideas?", "answer": "You can send a chocolate, or fruit, gift basket. Or ask if she needs anything; Like a maid service, or a delicious casserole dish? Or you can pay for an extra long distance phone call? Or let her stay a week as a guest at a hotel or your house until she gets on her feet?"}
{"question": "Do you honor birthdays with charitable giving requests?", "answer": "Yeah no."}
{"question": "How long do you keep birthday, Christmas cards for?", "answer": "i use them as fire starters in my wood stove after Little Christmas"}
{"question": "What is the best or most favorite gift you have ever received?", "answer": "My mom gave me the best sweaters, very warm and comfortable."}
{"question": "What should I buy for a house warming gift?", "answer": "A furnace?"}
{"question": "Can I use primer on a cardboard box before using acrylic paint? And is using primer/gesso necessary in this situation?", "answer": "As we advised on your earlier and very similar question, just take some other piece of cardboard and try it out."}
{"question": "Should I give something else to the neighbors for helping with the snow?", "answer": "How did they react to the wine?"}
{"question": "How are you expecting your Christmas, Chanukah and winter holidays will be different this year, or are you anticipating visiting like normal?", "answer": "I\u2019ll be staying home on my own. If there are some very mild days, I may have a friend or two over for socializing on the deck."}
{"question": "Is my wine still good?", "answer": "Safe? Yes. Good? ehhhh\u2026 Wine doesn\u2019t like getting hot."}
{"question": "So, jellies, let\u2019s discuss wrapping! Do you wrap? Fancy or simple? Are gift bags thoughtless and lazy or resource wise?", "answer": "I do wrap. I don\u2019t gift bag. I do it pretty simple. I don\u2019t bother with a bow, but I do sticker-labels. I sometimes use joke wrapping paper or joke gift boxes even though they\u2019re more expensive just to add an extra thing to talk about and have happen on the day."}
{"question": "Do you shop during the Thanksgiving weekend sales?", "answer": "Oh, lordy, never ever ever. I used to work retail, and I still hate the general frenetic miasma of the holiday sales weekends. I am a bit in awe of anyone willing to brave the crowds. It doesn\u2019t help that I am barely 5\u2019 tall, and bustling crowds make me feel like a lost toddler."}
{"question": "What would you do in this birthday party situation?", "answer": "I have found similar experiences to what you described, @janbb. Most people bring gifts and then I feel like an idiot. My suggestion, and what I will be doing in the future, is a gift card for a book store and maybe a small fun book in a gift bag. If, in the unlikely event that nobody else has brought a gift, you can kind of slip the gift to the host by placing it in a corner, quietly."}
{"question": "Have you ever heard of parents giving their children presents for Easter?", "answer": "Yes, but not at the level of Christmas or their Birthday. We always have my daughter Spring/Summer stuff, like a tee-shirt and flip flops or a beach towel and swim goggles. It had to fit in her basket though, along with some candy and such."}
{"question": "What sort of company makes wrapping paper with Titanic printed on it?", "answer": "Like this = = = > https://www.zazzle.com/titanic+ship+wrapping+paper"}
{"question": "Did you buy a gift for yourself this year?", "answer": "A nice set of kitchen knives. I haven\u2019t had the pleasure in years. Each time I got a new set my daughter would lose them, use them as lockpicks and screwdrivers, or, maybe I don\u2019t want to know what happened to the others.\nThe set I bought are nothing expensive, but nice."}
{"question": "What do you call giving a card to someone?", "answer": "I call giving a card to someone, giving a card to someone."}
{"question": "Is it really important to you to exchange holiday gifts with your friends?", "answer": "No. It was especially difficult when I had no money.\nI have no problem not receiving gifts, either.\nAnd your coworker is obtuse."}
{"question": "After a divorce or a major breakup, what have you done with any valuable gifts, such as jewelry?", "answer": "I have kept all the stuff that I/we shared when we were still together and I relish them as reminders, remembrances of how it was.\nSome I still take with me on travels, as good luck charms (also keepsakes from other people, other than my then partner).\n\nI should add that my ex partner and myself are friends, still."}
{"question": "Can you use watercolor pencils on cardboard?", "answer": "Sure you can. Whether the colors will actually be vivid enough to show, I don\u2019t know. Try it on another piece of cardboard if you don\u2019t want to try it on the box."}
{"question": "What kind of gifts, if any, do you exchange with your coworkers for the holidays?", "answer": "Last year we had a white elephant exchange, people brought wrapped presents, and we got numbers telling us who chose first. Some of the gifts were very nice, some silly, some goofy. It was a lot of fun."}
{"question": "Tis the season. Does your holiday gift list have fewer people on it this year than in years past?", "answer": "Not really. The only time I buy Christmas gifts is if I\u2019m doing Christmas with my husband\u2019s family or small gifts if I\u2019m invited to a gift exchange. We aren\u2019t going anywhere for Christmas this year."}
